[
  {
    "QuestionText": "1:**What is the closest planet to the Sun?",
    "AnswerText": "Mercury"
  },
  {
    "QuestionText": "2:**What is the second planet from the Sun?",
    "AnswerText": "Venus"
  },
  {
    "QuestionText": "3:**What is the planet known for its rings?",
    "AnswerText": "Saturn"
  },
  {
    "QuestionText": "4:**What is the largest planet in our solar system?",
    "AnswerText": "Jupiter"
  },
  {
    "QuestionText": "5:**What is the red planet?",
    "AnswerText": "Mars"
  },
  {
    "QuestionText": "6:**What is the planet known as the \"ice giant\"?",
    "AnswerText": "Uranus"
  },
  {
    "QuestionText": "7:**What is the furthest planet from the Sun (excluding Pluto)?",
    "AnswerText": "Neptune"
  },
  {
    "QuestionText": "8:**Which planet is known for its Great Red Spot?",
    "AnswerText": "Jupiter"
  },
  {
    "QuestionText": "9:**Which planet has the most moons?",
    "AnswerText": "Saturn"
  },
  {
    "QuestionText": "10:**Which planet is tilted on its side?",
    "AnswerText": "Uranus"
  },
  {
    "QuestionText": "11:**Which planet has a very strong magnetic field?",
    "AnswerText": "Jupiter"
  },
  {
    "QuestionText": "12:**Which planet is often called Earth's twin?",
    "AnswerText": "Venus"
  },
  {
    "QuestionText": "13:**Which planet has a very thin atmosphere?",
    "AnswerText": "Mercury"
  },
  {
    "QuestionText": "14:**Which planet is known for its strong winds?",
    "AnswerText": "Neptune"
  }
]